let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "fangen", "answer": "to catch", "options": ["to give up ( not Aufgabe  Task)", "to catch", "to invent", "to relocate"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "verbergen", "answer": "to cover, to hide kannada: Maremaachu", "options": ["to be located, to be situated", "to cover, to hide kannada: Maremaachu", "to acquire", "to complete"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "nachweisen", "answer": "to verify", "options": ["to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)", "to hide", "to verify", "to block, suspend"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "verbleiben", "answer": "to remain", "options": ["to mount", "to match kannada: hondisu", "to remain", "to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "abschliessen", "answer": "to complete", "options": ["entry in (in a form for example)", "to expand", "to complete", "to assign"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "behalten", "answer": "to keep, kannada: ittu KoLLu", "options": ["to carry", "to attune, kannada : dwanigoodu", "to keep, kannada: ittu KoLLu", "to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "urteilen", "answer": "to judge", "options": ["to be sufficient", "assume", "to judge", "to invent"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "sperren", "answer": "to block, suspend", "options": ["to spread", "to put, to place", "to expand", "to block, suspend"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "ausgeben", "answer": "to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)", "options": ["to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)", "to stop , kannada: tade hidi", "to transfer (money, power)", "to acquire"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "zuordnen", "answer": "to match kannada: hondisu", "options": ["to invent", "to agree", "to match kannada: hondisu", "evaluate (Bewertung rating)"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "entschliessen", "answer": "to determine", "options": ["to determine", "to hold", "to expand", "to quote"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "ausbauen", "answer": "to expand", "options": ["to expand", "to own", "to stop , kannada: tade hidi", "to pray (partizip 2: gebetet)"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "aufgeben", "answer": "to give up ( not Aufgabe  Task)", "options": ["to give details (Angabe   Details)", "to give up ( not Aufgabe  Task)", "evaluate (Bewertung rating)", "to be sufficient"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "verbereiten", "answer": "to spread", "options": ["to cover, to hide kannada: Maremaachu", "to own", "to spread", "to complete"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "\u00fcberweisen", "answer": "to transfer (money, power)", "options": ["to transfer (money, power)", "to dismiss", "to fill in (the blanks)", "to provide  (partizip 2 : geboten )"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "einbauen", "answer": "to mount", "options": ["to mount", "to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)", "to assign", "assume"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "fehlen", "answer": "to lack", "options": ["other than fact", "to reward", "to relocate", "to lack"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "dienen", "answer": "to serve", "options": ["to give details (Angabe   Details)", "to serve", "to determine", "to prove"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "verstecken", "answer": "to hide", "options": ["to give details (Angabe   Details)", "to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)", "to provide  (partizip 2 : geboten )", "to hide"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "tr\u00e4umen", "answer": "to dream", "options": ["to rethink kannada: aalochisu", "to hide", "to dream", "entry in (in a form for example)"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "anhalten", "answer": "to stop , kannada: tade hidi", "options": ["to serve", "to invent", "to give input (Eingabe Input)", "to stop , kannada: tade hidi"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "eintragen", "answer": "entry in (in a form for example)", "options": ["to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)", "to show ( partizip 2: gezeigt)", "entry in (in a form for example)", "to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "bedienen", "answer": "to operate", "options": ["to transfer (money, power)", "to receive", "to receive ( bekommen)", "to operate"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "zitieren", "answer": "to quote", "options": ["to be enough", "to match kannada: hondisu", "to give details (Angabe   Details)", "to quote"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "empfangen", "answer": "to receive", "options": ["to receive", "to own", "to verify", "to be enough"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "bitten", "answer": "to request  (partizip 2 : gebeten )", "options": ["evaluate (Bewertung rating)", "entry in (in a form for example)", "to determine", "to request  (partizip 2 : gebeten )"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "ahnen", "answer": "assume", "options": ["to be enough", "to request  (partizip 2 : gebeten )", "assume", "to catch"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "zeigen", "answer": "to show ( partizip 2: gezeigt)", "options": ["to dream", "to remain", "to receive", "to show ( partizip 2: gezeigt)"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "nachdenken", "answer": "to rethink kannada: aalochisu", "options": ["to own", "to carry", "to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)", "to rethink kannada: aalochisu"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "stimmen", "answer": "to attune, kannada : dwanigoodu", "options": ["to rethink kannada: aalochisu", "to dismiss", "to stop , kannada: tade hidi", "to attune, kannada : dwanigoodu"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "zeichnen", "answer": "to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)", "options": ["to draw ( partizip 2: gezeichnet)", "to operate", "to acquire", "to rethink kannada: aalochisu"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "versetzen", "answer": "to relocate", "options": ["to relocate", "to dismiss", "to provide  (partizip 2 : geboten )", "to operate"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "erg\u00e4nzen", "answer": "to fill in (the blanks)", "options": ["other than fact", "to request  (partizip 2 : gebeten )", "to fill in (the blanks)", "evaluate (Bewertung rating)"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "stellen", "answer": "to put, to place", "options": ["to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)", "to put, to place", "to dismiss", "to be located, to be situated"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "besitzen", "answer": "to own", "options": ["to judge", "to own", "to catch", "assume"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "erwerben", "answer": "to acquire", "options": ["to judge", "to acquire", "other than fact", "to assign"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "entlassen", "answer": "to dismiss", "options": ["to complete", "to dismiss", "to stick", "to rethink kannada: aalochisu"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "auszeichnen", "answer": "to reward", "options": ["to transfer (money, power)", "to reward", "to employ, engage", "to provide  (partizip 2 : geboten )"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "eingeben", "answer": "to give input (Eingabe Input)", "options": ["to give input (Eingabe Input)", "to spread", "to prove", "entry in (in a form for example)"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "bewerten", "answer": "evaluate (Bewertung rating)", "options": ["to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)", "to dream", "evaluate (Bewertung rating)", "to give details (Angabe   Details)"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "reichen", "answer": "to be enough", "options": ["to give details (Angabe   Details)", "to be located, to be situated", "to be enough", "to quote"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "stecken", "answer": "to stick", "options": ["to reward", "to fill in (the blanks)", "to complete", "to stick"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "versprechen", "answer": "to promise", "options": ["to cover, to hide kannada: Maremaachu", "to expand", "to promise", "to put, to place"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "erfinden", "answer": "to invent", "options": ["to relocate", "to discover", "to invent", "to be sufficient"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "beten", "answer": "to pray (partizip 2: gebetet)", "options": ["to expand", "to give input (Eingabe Input)", "to hold", "to pray (partizip 2: gebetet)"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "erhalten", "answer": "to receive ( bekommen)", "options": ["to reward", "evaluate (Bewertung rating)", "assume", "to receive ( bekommen)"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "befinden", "answer": "to be located, to be situated", "options": ["to carry", "to lack", "to be sufficient", "to be located, to be situated"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "ausreichen", "answer": "to be sufficient", "options": ["to be sufficient", "to pray (partizip 2: gebetet)", "to be enough", "to put, to place"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "tragen", "answer": "to carry", "options": ["to spend, also result ( Ausgabe)", "to assign", "to dream", "to carry"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "zustimmen", "answer": "to agree", "options": ["to cover, to hide kannada: Maremaachu", "to agree", "to give up ( not Aufgabe  Task)", "to prove"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "bieten", "answer": "to provide  (partizip 2 : geboten )", "options": ["to provide  (partizip 2 : geboten )", "to request  (partizip 2 : gebeten )", "to be enough", "to pray (partizip 2: gebetet)"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "angeben", "answer": "to give details (Angabe   Details)", "options": ["to be enough", "to give details (Angabe   Details)", "to give input (Eingabe Input)", "to receive ( bekommen)"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "halten", "answer": "to hold", "options": ["to hold", "to quote", "to match kannada: hondisu", "to reward"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "abgesehen davon", "answer": "other than fact", "options": ["to be enough", "to attune, kannada : dwanigoodu", "other than fact", "to operate"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "beweisen", "answer": "to prove", "options": ["to own", "to block, suspend", "to keep, kannada: ittu KoLLu", "to prove"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "zuweisen", "answer": "to assign", "options": ["to quote", "to assign", "to verify", "to stick"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "entdecken", "answer": "to discover", "options": ["to discover", "to acquire", "to rethink kannada: aalochisu", "to agree"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "anstellen", "answer": "to employ, engage", "options": ["to employ, engage", "to quote", "to put, to place", "to judge"]}];